(Sheldon:)Leonard,
(Sheldon:)they have a
sculpture gallery.
(Security Guard:)All right, I talked
to my supervisor,
(Security Guard:)and we're gonna let you go
with a warning.
(sighs in relief)
But if you ever
come back,
(Security Guard:)we will call the police
and press charges.
(Leonard:)We understand.
(Leonard:)Thank you so much.
(Nerdy Guy:)Uh, what about me?
(Security Guard:)No, you're not going
anywhere, kissy face.
(Security Guard:)Let's go.
(Security Guard:)I have to take your picture
to post at the guard gate.
(Sheldon:)Uh, one question
(Sheldon:)about that picture.
(Sheldon:)Can it be with
George Lucas?
(imitating Yoda):
Ooh, grumpy you are.
(Howard:)Okay, this is the match
that decides it all.
(Howard:)First to 11 wins.
(Howard:)Serve switches
every five points.
(Howard:)And just so you know,
when this started,
(Howard:)I was going to put the TARDIS in
a discreet corner of the house,
(Howard:)but I've since turned
mean, and now it's going
(Howard:)right in the middle
of the living room
(Howard:)on a rotating platform with
a sign that says "suck it."
(Howard:)Game on.
(Bernadette:)Except...
(Bernadette:)Raj is gonna win.